<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome! on The Digital Past</title>
    <link>http://amanda-regan.com/390summer18/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome! on The Digital Past</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#39;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/&#39; target=&#39;_blank&#39;&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;https://mirrors.creativecommons.org/presskit/icons/by.svg&#39; height=&#39;25&#39;&gt; Licensed CC-BY.&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://amanda-regan.com/390summer18/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>June 13th</title>
      <link>http://amanda-regan.com/390summer18/week2wed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://amanda-regan.com/390summer18/week2wed/</guid>
      <description>During Class
Pick one source from each category below and do a document analysis for it using the worksheets listed above. Post the answers on your blog and be prepared to discuss in class.
Worksheets:
 Cartoon Image Text  Text:
 Battle of the Triangle Fire Blame Shifted On All Sides For Fire Horror Hostile Employers See Yourselves as Others Know You Letter to Wm From Charles Willis Thompson  Images:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>http://amanda-regan.com/390summer18/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://amanda-regan.com/390summer18/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Week 1, Monday June 4th Topics:
 Introduction &amp;amp; Getting Started  After Class:
 Purchase a Student Plan ($30) from Reclaim Hosting Take the Student Technology Survey  Week 1, Wednesday June 6th Topics:
 What is Digital History? Building a Web Presence  Reading:
 Megan O’Neil, “Confronting the Myth of the ‘Digital Native’,” Chronicle of Higher Education, April 21, 2014. Miriam Posner, Stewart Varner, and Brian Coxall, “Creating Your Web Presence,” ProfHacker, February 14, 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assignments</title>
      <link>http://amanda-regan.com/390summer18/assignments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://amanda-regan.com/390summer18/assignments/</guid>
      <description>Assignment Due Date Grade Percentage     Quizzes Throughout the semester. 10%   Participation Throughout the semester. 10%   Blog Posts Throughout semester. 20%   Midterm July 2nd 20%   Skills Assessments TBD 8 @ 5% Each (40%)    Quizzes (10%): This course will include readings related to both the history of the Progressive Era and to Digital History. You should come to class prepared to discuss the readings listed on the syllabus for that day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post Rubric &amp; Criteria</title>
      <link>http://amanda-regan.com/390summer18/blogcriteria/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://amanda-regan.com/390summer18/blogcriteria/</guid>
      <description>Throughout the semester you will write a total of 6 blog posts. Each blog post will build on a topic discussed in class and they will often build on our in class tool tutorials. Blog posts will be due the following Sunday by 9:00am.
Your blog posts should be at least 350-500 words and should be written in a semi-formal scholarly style (complete thoughts, correct spelling, grammar and syntax.) Please use the Chicago style guide to cite any sources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policies</title>
      <link>http://amanda-regan.com/390summer18/policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://amanda-regan.com/390summer18/policies/</guid>
      <description>Communication Students are welcome to come to my office hours or to arrange an appointment at any time during the semester. All other course communication will take place in our Slack group. If you have registered for the course, and have not received an invitation in your email, please add yourself to the group using your Mason e-mail address. All course announcements will be posted to the #h390summer2018 channel and you are responsible for checking this venue regularly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>